(Penny:)My God, Leonard,
do you know
(Penny:)what I could do
with that kind of money?
(Leonard:)No, I do,
and that's why I hid it.
(Penny:)What good is it
if you don't use it?
Uh, uh, you have shoes
you love, but never wear.
(Leonard:)I have money I love,
(Leonard:)but never spend.
(Leonard:)We're kind of
a cute couple that way.
(Howard:)Again,
(Sheldon:)I'm sorry.
(Leonard:)I shouldn't have
kept it a secret.
(Penny:)Well, I have a secret
I've been keeping from you, too.
(Leonard:)Is it a secret bank account?
(Leonard:)Because that would be awesome.
(Penny:)I hate my job.
(Howard:)Really?
(Leonard:)Why?
(Penny:)Because I don't feel good
(Penny:)flirting with doctors for sales.
(Penny:)I mean, I know
I make a lot of money.
(Penny:)But I haven't been happy
for a while.
(Leonard:)Why didn't you tell me?
(Penny:)Because I know
how important it is to you
(Penny:)that I'm having some success.
(Leonard:)That's not true.
(Penny:)Okay, really?
So you'd be fine if I went
(Penny:)back to acting
and waiting tables again?
(Leonard:)If that's what you
want to do, yes.
(Penny:)Well, it's not
what I want to do.
(Leonard:)Oh, yes.
(Penny:)Doesn't matter what I want.
(Penny:)Look, this job is
gonna get me out of debt.